<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Swy.me]]></title>
  <link href="http://swy.me/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://swy.me/"/>
  <updated>2013-02-10T23:20:42-08:00</updated>
  <id>http://swy.me/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Stephen Way]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[BrowserStack Bookmarklets]]></title>
    <link href="http://swy.me/blog/2012/10/12/browserstack-bookmarklets/"/>
    <updated>2012-10-12T10:12:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://swy.me/blog/2012/10/12/browserstack-bookmarklets</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;ve been so busy lately I forgot to report on my latest release, it&#8217;s not groundbreaking but definitely useful!</p>

<p>BrowserStack is a service that provides cross-browser, cross-mobile testing to developers who need to test javascript and/or css. I thought it was so handy that I wanted to cut out some of the time I was spending with URLs and just get a set of bookmarks that let me call up a browser from the current site I was on. This is a complete set of browsers offered on this service.</p>

<p>To use, <a href="http://www.github.com/stephenway/browserstack-bookmarklets">Clone My GitHub Project</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google to drop support for IE8 in Nov.]]></title>
    <link href="http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/15/google-to-drop-support-for-ie8-on-nov-15/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-15T19:27:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/15/google-to-drop-support-for-ie8-on-nov-15</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Gregg Keizer writing for Computerworld:</p>

<blockquote><p>Google will drop support for Microsoft&#8217;s Internet Explorer 8 (IE8) for its online apps and services in mid-November, effectively ending support for many users of Windows XP.</p></blockquote>


<p>Sounds like a good plan to me.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[iOS 6]]></title>
    <link href="http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/12/ios-6/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-12T11:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/12/ios-6</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today Apple announced a major update to it&#8217;s mobile operating system iOS. I&#8217;ve been using iOS 6 Beta for the past 3 months on my iPhone 4S and iPad 2 and I have to say it does improve upon some of the core apps that have shipped since the first iPhone. It also comes with one new app and many improved features.</p>

<p>The user interface (UIKit) has gotten an update in how it handles the color of the system and app title bar. Now when an app has a colored title bar the system bar gets a slightly darker shade of the same color.</p>

<h2>Maps</h2>

<p>For years we have had a Google powered Maps app. Now it&#8217;s powered by TomTom data and Apple&#8217;s new maps. With the brand new maps app, Apple has also included a navigation feature for getting directions. Having used TomTom&#8217;s own navigation app and MotionX, it&#8217;s a joy using Maps navigation. The refresh rate is almost un-noticeable because the animation is smooth. Although they still have to work on the data side of things (I did get lost in the country one time with it.), overall a great new version of the Maps app.</p>

<h2>Shared Photostreams</h2>

<p>A nice improvement to Photostreams is also packed into iOS 6 for touch devices and AppleTV. I&#8217;m going to skip over the comments and notifications, I don&#8217;t think Apple wants to replace Facebook or anything with these basic features.</p>

<p>My main AppleTV has always been set to my Photostream, but with all the screen-shots and wallpaper I save to my camera roll the more gunk-ed up my Photostream gets. With Shared Photostreams I can finally make a screen-saver Photostream and put all the photos I want on it instead of the whole camera roll.</p>

<h2>Passbook</h2>

<p>The new app in iOS 6 that will hopefully make your wallet fit in a Slimmy, clip or rubber band. Passbook is the first step to eliminating your physical wallet.</p>

<p>My first use case was at Best Buy, I was helping a friend out with a Mac purchase (there are no Apple Stores in Bend, OR) and I picked up some Sodastream flavors, once I got to checkout the guy asked for my rewards zone card, I quickly pulled out my phone and parked it on his register with my Rewards Zone card open in Passbook. He pulled out his scanner and tried scanning the bar-code on the card, but it was a different type of bar-code, so he manually entered in the member number. I think it will be interesting to see what Best Buy actually releases for an official Passbook card because I don&#8217;t think the regular bar-codes are supported.</p>

<p>Second use case was at the local theater. Same thing happened, bar-code wouldn&#8217;t scan and the employee had to enter the number manually. With that in mind, I think the world has some adjusting to do before we can all ditch our cards, but as long as the ID number is on your Passbook card you always have that to fall back on.</p>

<p>There are a couple things that will ruin your battery life with Passbook, location access and automatic updates for cards. For some reason I would use up a whole charge within 4 hours. This was enough of a setback for me to turn all that extra functionality off.</p>

<h2>Facetime</h2>

<p>Would be useful if my carrier AT&amp;T didn&#8217;t block over cellular. However it performs perfectly if it&#8217;s enabled.</p>

<h2>Phone</h2>

<p>Do Not Disturb blocks all those annoying calls and notifications at night, or whenever you switch it on. There was only one time where an unknown caller called me twice in my area after Do Not Disturb had been turned on, so I know it works great.</p>

<h2>Mail</h2>

<p>Attachments are more accessible inside the Mail app, something I&#8217;ve wanting for years. People just think that way about VIP contacts seems like a Google</p>

<h2>Safari</h2>

<p>New version of Safari has a noticeable increase in page load times and javascript performance. The most noticeable improvement is landscape full-screen. There is so much more you can see in that view.</p>

<h2>Conclusion</h2>

<p>This could be called the &#8220;back to our roots&#8221; update by improving the core apps once again, and by adding Passbook, which is a big leap forward even if the world isn&#8217;t ready for it, I suspect it will get more attention over the next year.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sublime Text vs. Chocolat]]></title>
    <link href="http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/12/sublime-vs-chocolat/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-12T09:32:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/12/sublime-vs-chocolat</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>If I were comparing the two I would use these links as a major deciding point.</p>

<p><a href="http://wbond.net/sublime_packages/community">Sublime Text Packages</a> &amp; <a href="http://mixins.chocolatapp.com/mixins/browse/">Cocolat Mixins</a></p>

<p>The difference is incredible.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPhone 5]]></title>
    <link href="http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/12/iphone-5/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-12T08:57:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/12/iphone-5</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When I look at how big this thing is, I just think about how nice my 4S feels in my hand just using one hand. However I do have some big hands, I can easily touch any part of the screen with one hand. It&#8217;s important, using one hand when I&#8217;m holding my son, or holding a drink while I skim over the morning Twitter feed. The true test is always going to the Apple Store and holding one in your hand to see if it could be a match.</p>

<h2>Ultrafast Wireless</h2>

<p>I&#8217;ve never actually used a true LTE device, but I heard it&#8217;s almost like WiFi which is great (Apple used the phrase, &#8220;&hellip;in some cases, better than WiFI.&#8221;). When a carrier comes out with a family friendly pool plan, one connection, all devices for up to 4-5 people I doubt people in the know will keep their broadband connection.</p>

<h2>A6</h2>

<p>To be expected, however the graphics seem to be similar quality to the Xbox 360. Can&#8217;t wait to play some newer games and find out how responsive it is, how clear the game looks.</p>

<p>Overall, I think this is a great device, but I&#8217;ll wait for NFC next year.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing Websites in Game Console Browsers]]></title>
    <link href="http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/11/testing-websites-in-game-console-browsers/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-11T12:42:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/11/testing-websites-in-game-console-browsers</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Anna Debenham writing for A List Apart:</p>

<blockquote><p>More than one in eight internet users in the UK, US, and France—and nearly one in four American teens—uses a game console to get online, according to studies from 2010 and 2011.</p></blockquote>


<p>I have at least two of these devices at home, but I&#8217;m not suddenly going to go out and buy them all to make sure they all work. Maybe this would be more realistic if we had device simulators.</p>

<p>The article does take a nice spin into progressive enhancement, and I think it&#8217;s a good idea just to test your favorite work at least once in whatever gaming device you have available.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bower]]></title>
    <link href="http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/11/bower/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-11T07:16:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/11/bower</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Speaking of Yeoman, there is also a new package manager called Bower. It lets you install assets into your app like jQuery or backbone.</p>

<figure class='code'> <div class="highlight"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre class="line-numbers"><span class='line-number'>1</span>
<span class='line-number'>2</span>
<span class='line-number'>3</span>
<span class='line-number'>4</span>
</pre></td><td class='code'><pre><code class='sh'><span class='line'><span class="nv">$ </span>bower install jquery
</span><span class='line'><span class="nv">$ </span>bower install git://github.com/maccman/package-jquery.git
</span><span class='line'><span class="nv">$ </span>bower install http://code.jquery.com/jquery-1.7.2.js
</span><span class='line'><span class="nv">$ </span>bower install ./repos/jquery
</span></code></pre></td></tr></table></div></figure>


<p>For those of you familiar with Sublime Text&#8217;s <a href="http://wbond.net/sublime_packages/package_control">3rd party package manager</a>, this is a breath of fresh air for managing projects in a shell.</p>

<p>I didn&#8217;t link to it&#8217;s homepage because it&#8217;s just an <a href="http://twitter.github.com/bower/">image and a button</a>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yeoman]]></title>
    <link href="http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/10/yeoman/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-10T11:48:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/10/yeoman</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A new front-end toolset, available today.</p>

<blockquote><p>Yeoman is a robust and opinionated set of tools, libraries, and a workflow that can help developers quickly build beautiful, compelling web apps.</p></blockquote>


<p>Simply open your shell and run:</p>

<figure class='code'> <div class="highlight"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre class="line-numbers"><span class='line-number'>1</span>
</pre></td><td class='code'><pre><code class='sh'><span class='line'><span class="nv">$ </span>curl -L get.yeoman.io | bash
</span></code></pre></td></tr></table></div></figure>


<p>Then to start a project, make a new directory and run:</p>

<figure class='code'> <div class="highlight"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre class="line-numbers"><span class='line-number'>1</span>
</pre></td><td class='code'><pre><code class='sh'><span class='line'><span class="nv">$ </span>yeoman init
</span></code></pre></td></tr></table></div></figure>


<p>Note: If you already have node.js and NPM, upgrade them before installing Yeoman.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tango Down]]></title>
    <link href="http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/10/tango-down/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-10T11:48:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/10/tango-down</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote><p>#TangoDown &#8211; http://www.godaddy.com/  | by @AnonymousOwn3r |</p><footer><strong>@AnonOpsLegion</strong> <cite><a href='https://twitter.com/AnonOpsLegion/status/245218636187443200'>twitter.com/AnonOpsLegion/&hellip;</a></cite></footer></blockquote>


<p>I really need to get off GoDaddy.</p>

<p>This hacker news thread is also a good resource for some free alternative DNS services if you don&#8217;t want to pay transfer fees.</p>

<p>Update: Moved DNS over to Zerigo, just in time for the third timeout on GoDaddy. Cheers!</p>

<p>Update 2: <a href="http://www.wired.com/wiredenterprise/2012/09/godaddy-moves-to-verisign/">More details</a> on the outage as GoDaddy itself moves it&#8217;s own DNS to Verisign.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Years of Zen Coding]]></title>
    <link href="http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/09/four-years-of-zen-coding/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-09T21:16:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/09/four-years-of-zen-coding</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Chris Coyier on Emmet for Sublime Text:</p>

<blockquote><p>Zen Coding is being sunset and is now Emmet. For sublime: https://github.com/sergeche/emmet-sublime &hellip; New features for CSS like w100p -> width: 100%;</p><footer><strong>@chriscoyier</strong> <cite><a href='https://twitter.com/chriscoyier/statuses/244904994216767491'>twitter.com/chriscoyier/&hellip;</a></cite></footer></blockquote>


<p>Zen Coding was a huge leap forward for web designers when it was first released, among the many text editors it extended, it contributed to the rise of TextMate. I would be curious to see some numbers that show what text editor all the ex-TextMate users are using, I have a hunch the majority is Sublime Text. <a href="https://github.com/sergeche/emmet-sublime">Link to Emmet for Sublime Text</a></p>

<p>Heres the original Smashing Magazine post from the creator Sergey Chikuyonok in 2009: <a href="http://coding.smashingmagazine.com/2009/11/21/zen-coding-a-new-way-to-write-html-code/">Zen Coding: A Speedy Way To Write HTML/CSS Code</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[AT&amp;T’s FaceTime Blocking Hurts the Deaf]]></title>
    <link href="http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/08/at-and-ts-facetime-blocking-hurts-the-deaf/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-08T14:01:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/08/at-and-ts-facetime-blocking-hurts-the-deaf</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Brendan Grammer writing for Wired:</p>

<blockquote><p>It’s disappointing that AT&T is standing in the way of innovation that addresses the needs of its deaf and hard-of-hearing customers. Sometimes it takes a while (and some prodding) for technology and technology companies to catch up to and embrace accessibility. In this case the technology is there, but it’s AT&T that’s throwing up the barrier.</p></blockquote>


<p>There are no technical limitations based on what plan you purchase to use FaceTime over cellular. AT&amp;T doesn&#8217;t want to see their revenue from voice plans go away. That moment I recieved my first FaceTime call from my Dad not being on a Wi-Fi network was definitely magical. I hope the deaf community will get that experience soon.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoffeeScript Source Maps]]></title>
    <link href="http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/08/coffeescript-source-maps/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-08T10:20:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/08/coffeescript-source-maps</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote><p>That’s it!</p><p>When you go to “Sources” in web inspector for a web page that includes test.js it will now show your CoffeeScript source files where you can set break points, hover variables to see their values, etc.</p></blockquote>


<p>CoffeeScript just came full-circle. What more could we ask for?</p>

<p>Check out this tutorial in case your not in the loop on <a href="http://www.html5rocks.com/en/tutorials/developertools/sourcemaps/">Javascript Source Maps</a>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finally]]></title>
    <link href="http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/07/finally/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-07T19:28:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/07/finally</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Reviewers getting started early this year on the anticipation of iOS 6. This could amount to an anxiety attack.</p>

<p>Follow up from <a href="http://daringfireball.net/linked/2011/06/21/finally">&#9733; DF</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Inspector: Implement SCSS source highlighter]]></title>
    <link href="http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/07/web-inspector-implement-scss-source-highlighter/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-07T18:01:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/07/web-inspector-implement-scss-source-highlighter</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Alexander Pavlov on the Chromium team:</p>

<blockquote><p>This change modifies the existing CSS highlighter to support SCSS as well. The &#8220;text/x-scss&#8221; mime-type is assigned to SASSSource.</p></blockquote>


<p>Certainly a huge step forward for the Sass core team.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Simple Progress Bar]]></title>
    <link href="http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/07/a-simple-progress-bar/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-07T17:44:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/07/a-simple-progress-bar</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is an impressive use of CSS applied to just one HTML progress tag.</p>

<figure class='code'> <div class="highlight"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre class="line-numbers"><span class='line-number'>1</span>
<span class='line-number'>2</span>
<span class='line-number'>3</span>
<span class='line-number'>4</span>
<span class='line-number'>5</span>
<span class='line-number'>6</span>
<span class='line-number'>7</span>
<span class='line-number'>8</span>
<span class='line-number'>9</span>
<span class='line-number'>10</span>
<span class='line-number'>11</span>
<span class='line-number'>12</span>
<span class='line-number'>13</span>
<span class='line-number'>14</span>
<span class='line-number'>15</span>
<span class='line-number'>16</span>
<span class='line-number'>17</span>
<span class='line-number'>18</span>
<span class='line-number'>19</span>
<span class='line-number'>20</span>
<span class='line-number'>21</span>
<span class='line-number'>22</span>
<span class='line-number'>23</span>
<span class='line-number'>24</span>
<span class='line-number'>25</span>
<span class='line-number'>26</span>
<span class='line-number'>27</span>
<span class='line-number'>28</span>
<span class='line-number'>29</span>
<span class='line-number'>30</span>
<span class='line-number'>31</span>
<span class='line-number'>32</span>
<span class='line-number'>33</span>
<span class='line-number'>34</span>
<span class='line-number'>35</span>
<span class='line-number'>36</span>
<span class='line-number'>37</span>
<span class='line-number'>38</span>
<span class='line-number'>39</span>
<span class='line-number'>40</span>
<span class='line-number'>41</span>
<span class='line-number'>42</span>
</pre></td><td class='code'><pre><code class='css'><span class='line'><span class="k">@-webkit-keyframes</span> <span class="nt">m</span> <span class="p">{</span>
</span><span class='line'>  <span class="nt">0</span><span class="o">%</span> <span class="p">{</span><span class="k">background-position</span><span class="o">:</span><span class="m">20px</span> <span class="m">0</span><span class="p">}</span> <span class="nt">100</span><span class="o">%</span> <span class="p">{}</span>
</span><span class='line'><span class="p">}</span>
</span><span class='line'><span class="k">@-moz-keyframes</span> <span class="nt">m</span> <span class="p">{</span>
</span><span class='line'>  <span class="nt">0</span><span class="o">%</span> <span class="p">{</span><span class="k">background-position</span><span class="o">:</span><span class="m">20px</span> <span class="m">0</span><span class="p">}</span> <span class="nt">100</span><span class="o">%</span> <span class="p">{</span><span class="k">background-position</span><span class="o">:</span><span class="m">0</span> <span class="m">0</span><span class="p">}</span>
</span><span class='line'><span class="p">}</span>
</span><span class='line'><span class="nt">body</span> <span class="p">{</span>
</span><span class='line'>  <span class="k">background</span><span class="o">:</span><span class="k">rgb</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="m">235</span><span class="o">,</span><span class="m">235</span><span class="o">,</span><span class="m">240</span><span class="p">);</span>
</span><span class='line'><span class="p">}</span>
</span><span class='line'><span class="nt">progress</span> <span class="p">{</span>
</span><span class='line'>  <span class="k">position</span><span class="o">:</span><span class="k">absolute</span><span class="p">;</span>
</span><span class='line'>  <span class="k">left</span><span class="o">:</span><span class="m">50</span><span class="o">%</span><span class="p">;</span>
</span><span class='line'>  <span class="k">top</span><span class="o">:</span><span class="m">50</span><span class="o">%</span><span class="p">;</span>
</span><span class='line'>  <span class="k">margin</span><span class="o">:-</span><span class="m">20px</span> <span class="m">0</span> <span class="m">0</span> <span class="m">-31px</span><span class="p">;</span>
</span><span class='line'>  <span class="k">width</span><span class="o">:</span><span class="m">62px</span><span class="p">;</span>
</span><span class='line'>  <span class="k">height</span><span class="o">:</span><span class="m">12px</span><span class="p">;</span>
</span><span class='line'>  <span class="k">border</span><span class="o">:</span><span class="m">1px</span> <span class="k">solid</span> <span class="k">rgb</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="m">160</span><span class="o">,</span><span class="m">170</span><span class="o">,</span><span class="m">190</span><span class="p">);</span>
</span><span class='line'>  <span class="k">border</span><span class="o">-</span><span class="n">radius</span><span class="o">:</span><span class="m">6px</span><span class="p">;</span>
</span><span class='line'>  <span class="k">background</span><span class="o">:</span>
</span><span class='line'>    <span class="o">-</span><span class="n">webkit</span><span class="o">-</span><span class="n">radial</span><span class="o">-</span><span class="n">gradient</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="n">rgba</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="m">140</span><span class="o">,</span><span class="m">153</span><span class="o">,</span><span class="m">172</span><span class="o">,.</span><span class="m">3</span><span class="p">)</span><span class="o">,</span> <span class="n">rgba</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="m">140</span><span class="o">,</span><span class="m">153</span><span class="o">,</span><span class="m">172</span><span class="o">,</span><span class="m">0</span><span class="p">))</span><span class="o">,</span>
</span><span class='line'>    <span class="o">-</span><span class="n">webkit</span><span class="o">-</span><span class="n">linear</span><span class="o">-</span><span class="n">gradient</span><span class="p">(</span>
</span><span class='line'>      <span class="m">#fff</span> <span class="m">15</span><span class="o">%,</span> <span class="m">#e9ecf1</span> <span class="m">15</span><span class="o">%,</span> <span class="m">#d2d9e1</span> <span class="m">50</span><span class="o">%,</span> <span class="m">#bdc6d2</span> <span class="m">50</span><span class="o">%,</span> <span class="m">#dfe7ed</span>
</span><span class='line'>    <span class="p">);</span>
</span><span class='line'>  <span class="k">background</span><span class="o">:</span>
</span><span class='line'>    <span class="o">-</span><span class="n">moz</span><span class="o">-</span><span class="n">radial</span><span class="o">-</span><span class="n">gradient</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="n">rgba</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="m">140</span><span class="o">,</span><span class="m">153</span><span class="o">,</span><span class="m">172</span><span class="o">,.</span><span class="m">3</span><span class="p">)</span><span class="o">,</span> <span class="n">rgba</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="m">140</span><span class="o">,</span><span class="m">153</span><span class="o">,</span><span class="m">172</span><span class="o">,</span><span class="m">0</span><span class="p">))</span><span class="o">,</span>
</span><span class='line'>    <span class="o">-</span><span class="n">moz</span><span class="o">-</span><span class="n">linear</span><span class="o">-</span><span class="n">gradient</span><span class="p">(</span>
</span><span class='line'>      <span class="m">#fff</span> <span class="m">15</span><span class="o">%,</span> <span class="m">#e9ecf1</span> <span class="m">15</span><span class="o">%,</span> <span class="m">#d2d9e1</span> <span class="m">50</span><span class="o">%,</span> <span class="m">#bdc6d2</span> <span class="m">50</span><span class="o">%,</span> <span class="m">#dfe7ed</span>
</span><span class='line'>    <span class="p">);</span>
</span><span class='line'>  <span class="k">background</span><span class="o">-</span><span class="k">size</span><span class="o">:</span><span class="m">20px</span> <span class="m">10px</span><span class="p">;</span>
</span><span class='line'>  <span class="n">box</span><span class="o">-</span><span class="n">shadow</span><span class="o">:</span><span class="m">0</span> <span class="m">1px</span> <span class="m">0</span> <span class="n">rgba</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="m">255</span><span class="o">,</span><span class="m">255</span><span class="o">,</span><span class="m">255</span><span class="o">,.</span><span class="m">9</span><span class="p">);</span>
</span><span class='line'>  <span class="o">-</span><span class="n">webkit</span><span class="o">-</span><span class="n">animation</span><span class="o">:</span><span class="n">m</span> <span class="m">.6s</span> <span class="n">linear</span> <span class="n">infinite</span><span class="p">;</span>
</span><span class='line'>  <span class="o">-</span><span class="n">moz</span><span class="o">-</span><span class="n">animation</span><span class="o">:</span><span class="n">m</span> <span class="m">.6s</span> <span class="n">linear</span> <span class="n">infinite</span><span class="p">;</span>
</span><span class='line'><span class="p">}</span>
</span><span class='line'><span class="o">:</span><span class="nd">:-webkit-progress-bar</span> <span class="p">{</span>
</span><span class='line'>  <span class="k">display</span><span class="o">:</span><span class="k">none</span><span class="p">;</span>
</span><span class='line'><span class="p">}</span>
</span><span class='line'><span class="o">:</span><span class="nd">:-moz-progress-bar</span> <span class="p">{</span>
</span><span class='line'>  <span class="k">visibility</span><span class="o">:</span><span class="k">hidden</span><span class="p">;</span>
</span><span class='line'><span class="p">}</span>
</span><span class='line'><span class="k">@-moz-document</span> <span class="nt">url-prefix</span><span class="o">(</span><span class="nt">http</span><span class="o">://)</span> <span class="p">{</span>
</span><span class='line'>  <span class="nt">progress</span> <span class="p">{</span><span class="k">width</span><span class="o">:</span><span class="m">60px</span><span class="p">;</span> <span class="k">height</span><span class="o">:</span><span class="m">10px</span><span class="p">;}</span>
</span><span class='line'><span class="p">}</span>
</span></code></pre></td></tr></table></div></figure>


<p>Via <a href="deaxon.com">Benjamin De Cock</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything is a Module]]></title>
    <link href="http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/07/everything-is-a-module/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-07T14:05:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/07/everything-is-a-module</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Drew Barontini talks about learning to stay modular in his stylesheets for application development, for instance simplifying a collection of content like a comment or review or user block and making reusable styles that are general to all of them.</p>

<blockquote><p>I found myself repeating this pattern multiple times throughout the application that I am currently working on.</p></blockquote>


<p>This seems like it could have been a lesson in CSS pre-processor mixins or @extend.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung should make its own smartphone OS]]></title>
    <link href="http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/07/samsung-should-make-its-own-smartphone-os/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-07T11:58:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/07/samsung-should-make-its-own-smartphone-os</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>If you don&#8217;t remember Samsung created Bada OS which ended in a slow death.</p>

<blockquote><p>On the other hand, while once-mighty mobile giants like RIM and Microsoft are already fighting for third place, both companies have struggled with delays — so third place could be a low-hanging fruit for a competent contender.</p></blockquote>


<p>Samsung would have a chance at starting over for a chance at third place if it were not so late to the after party.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Seeks to Create Pandora Rival]]></title>
    <link href="http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/06/apple-seeks-to-create-pandora-rival/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-06T17:33:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/06/apple-seeks-to-create-pandora-rival</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote><p>Apple Inc. is in talks to license music for a custom-radio service similar to the popular one operated by Pandora Media Inc., according to people familiar with the matter, in what would be a bid by the hardware maker to expand its dominance in online music.</p></blockquote>


<p>I see Apple working on 3 potential apps to be included in or alongside iTunes:</p>

<ul>
<li>Video sharing service (YouTube)</li>
<li>Music recognition (Shazam)</li>
<li>Radio (Pandora)</li>
</ul>


<p>I think the latter would be the easiest for them to release this year. Also, wouldn&#8217;t be hard for them to raise the bar over Pandora and Spotify with the iTunes Store catalog.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deadweight]]></title>
    <link href="http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/06/deadweight/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-06T15:36:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/06/deadweight</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote><p>Deadweight is a CSS coverage tool. Given a set of stylesheets and a set of URLs, it determines which selectors are actually used and reports which can be &#8220;safely&#8221; deleted.</p><p><figure class='code'><figcaption><span>How to Use It</span></figcaption><div class="highlight"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre class="line-numbers"><span class='line-number'>1</span><br/><span class='line-number'>2</span><br/><span class='line-number'>3</span><br/></pre></td><td class='code'><pre><code class='sh'><span class='line'><span class="nv">$ </span>deadweight -s styles.css -s ie.css index.html about.html<br/></span><span class='line'><span class="nv">$ </span>deadweight -s http://www.tigerbloodwins.com/index.css http://www.tigerbloodwins.com/<br/></span><span class='line'><span class="nv">$ </span>deadweight --root http://kottke.org/ -s <span class="s1">&#39;/templates/2009/css.php?p=mac&#39;</span> / /everfresh /about<br/></span></code></pre></td></tr></table></div></figure></p></blockquote>


<p>Using this for a few minutes will really clean up your stylsheets.</p>

<p>Via <a href="http://www.kungfugrippe.com/post/31002931568">Mr. Mann Merlin Mann</a> Way of the future</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[@mrdoob's realtime editor]]></title>
    <link href="http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/06/at-mrdoobs-realtime-editor/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-06T12:56:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://swy.me/blog/2012/09/06/at-mrdoobs-realtime-editor</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote><p>Love @mrdoob&#8217;s realtime editor http://mrdoob.com/projects/code-editor/ … Also: offline-enabled! Bonus: he wrote on his inspirations http://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=4478618</p><footer><strong>@paul_irish</strong> <cite><a href='https://twitter.com/paul_irish/statuses/243798388271898624'>twitter.com/paul_irish/statuses/&hellip;</a></cite></footer></blockquote>


<p>This looks like a TextMate web-app. Just pure fun to make I&#8217;m sure.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
